<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Campus Food</string>
    <string name="app_heading">Locations</string>
    <string name="hours_lowerCafe"><![CDATA[
    <p><i><b>Operation Hours</b></i></p>
    <p>Monday - Thursday: 11:00 a.m. - 7:00 p.m.</p>
    <p>Friday: 11:00 a.m. - 3:00 p.m.</p>
    Saturday - Sunday: Closed]]></string>
    <string name="hours_Deloitte"><![CDATA[
    <p><i><b>Operation Hours</b></i></p>
    <p>Monday - Thursday: 7:30 a.m. - 9:30 p.m.</p>
    <p>Friday: 7:30 a.m. - 4:00 p.m.</p>
    <p>Saturday: 11:00 a.m. - 5:00 p.m.</p>
    Sunday: 12:00 p.m. - 9:00 p.m.]]></string>
    <string name ="hours_921"><![CDATA[
    <p><i><b>Operation Hours</b></i></p>
    <p>Monday - Thursday: 7:00 a.m. - 9:00 p.m.</p>
    <p>Friday: 7:00 a.m. - 8:00 p.m.</p>
    <p>Saturday: 9:00 a.m. - 8:00 p.m.</p>
    Sunday: 9:00 a.m. - 9:00 p.m.]]></string>
    <string name ="hours_currito"><![CDATA[
     <p><i><b>Operation Hours</b></i></p>
     <p>Monday - Thursday, Sunday: 12:00 p.m. - 11:00 p.m.</p>
    Friday - Saturday: 12:00 p.m. - 7:00 p.m.]]></string>
    <string name ="hours_dunkin"><![CDATA[
    <p><i><b>Operation Hours</b></i></p>
    <p>Monday - Thursday: 7:00 a.m. - 8:00 p.m.</p>
    <p>Friday: 7:00 a.m. - 6:00 p.m.</p>
    Saturday - Sunday: 8:00 a.m. - 6:00 p.m.
    ]]></string>
    <string name ="menu_lowerCafe"><![CDATA[
    <p><i><b>Menu</b></i></p>
    <p>Monday: Assorted Sandwiches Snack & Beverage</p>
    <p>Tuesday: Porchetta (GF) OR Vegetarian: Eggplant Parmesan With: Roasted Potatoes (GF) Snack & Beverage</p>
    <p>Wednesday: Herb Roasted Turkey (GF) OR Vegetarian: Butternut Squash & Lentils (GF) With Roasted Corn (GF) Snack & Beverage</p>
    <p>Thursday: Mediterranean Salmon (GF) OR Vegetarian: Shepard’s Pie (GF) With: Rice Pilaf Snack & Beverage</p>
    ]]></string>
    <string name ="menu_921"><![CDATA[
    <p><i><b>Menu</b></i></p>
    <p>Fresh fruit and salads</p>
    <p>Delicious, hot, home-style entrées</p>
    <p>Simple Servings Allergen Station</p>
    <p>Freshly baked pizza and pasta</p>
    <p>Deli choices served on freshly baked breads</p>
    <p>New creations by our chef just for you Ice cream and freshly baked desserts</p>
    <p>Homemade soups and you can enjoy "all you care to eat"!</p>
    <p>A Better Tomorrow ‘For Your Health’ Plates</p>
    ]]></string>
    <string name ="menu_Deloitte"><![CDATA[
    <p><i><b>Menu</b></i></p>
    <p><b>Bagels:</b> Classic. Thinfastic. Signature. Gourmet</p>
    <p><b>Breakfast:</b> Egg Sandwiches. Egg Sandwiches with Cheese Only. Egg Paninis. Egg Wraps. Thintastic Eggwhites</p>
    <p><b>Lunch:</b> Deli. Signature. Hot Paninis. Bagel Melts with Turkey & Cheddar. Bagel Melts with
     Pepperoni Pizza. Bagel Melts with Cheese Pizza.</p>
    <p><b>Hot, Iced or Frozen(Signature):</b> Vanilla Hazelnut Latte. White Chocolate Mocca. White
     Chocolate Mocca. Caramel Macchiato. Caramel Macchiato. Vanilla Cream Latte</p>
    <p><b>Hot, Iced or Frozen (Classic):</b> Latte. Mocha. Chai Tea Latte. Cappuccino. Hot, Iced
     or Frozen. Fresh-Brewed Coffee. Iced Coffee. Green Tea. Hot Chocolate. Real Fruit Smoothie. Fountain & Iced Tea.</p>
    ]]></string>
    <string name="menu_currito"><![CDATA[
    <p><i><b>Menu</b></i></p>
    <p><b>Choose one:</b> bowl. flour tortilla. whole wheat tortilla<p>
    <p><b>Protein:</b> grilled chicken. grilled steak. braised beef. pulled pork. organic tofu</p>
    <p><b>Add ingredients: </b> kale. quinoa.</p>
    <p><b>Rice: </b> cilantro lime rice. white rice. brown rice<p>
    <p><b>Beans: </b> black beans. pinto beans. curried chick peas</p>
    <p><b>Salsa: </b> mango salsa. pico de gallo. corn salsa</p>
    <p><b>Toppings: </b> blue cheese celery slaw. house made hummus. Almond. sherbed croutons. rice
     noodles. sesame seeds. jack cheese. feta cheese. sour cream</p>
    <p><b>Dressings: </b> skinny mediterranean vinaigrette. creamy lime dressing. asian vinaigrette.
     blue cheese dressing. balsamic dressing. caesar dressing. ranch dressing</p>
    <p><b>Veggies: </b> bok choy. asian slaw. romaine lettuce. Cucumber. Broccoli. Celery. caramelized
     onions. shredded carrots. scallions</p>
    ]]></string>
    <string name="menu_dunkin"><![CDATA[
    <p><i><b>Menu</b></i></p>
    <p><b>Donut</b> Fudge Croissant Donut. Bagel with Cream Cheese. Sausage, Egg & Cheese on a Croisssant
     - with Hash Browns. Bacon, Egg & Cheese on a Bagel - with Hash Browns. Veggie Egg White Flatbread.
      Ham, Egg & Cheese on an English Muffin - with Hash Browns. Big n\' Toasted - with Hash Browns. Wake-Up Wrap
       (Bacon, Ham, or Sausage). Turkey Sausage Flatbread with Hash Browns.</p>
    <p><b>DD Combos</b> Snack N\' Go Chicken Wrap. Combos Include Small Iced Tea. Snack N\' Go Steak
     Wrap. Ham & Cheese Flatbread - with Hash Browns. Deluxe Grilled Cheese (Ham or Bacon) - with Hash Browns.
      Turkey, Cheddar & Bacon Flatbread - with Hash Browns. Chicken Salad or Tuna Salad Sandwich - with Hash Browns.
       Chicken Bacon Sandwich - with Hash Browns. Classic Egg & Cheese. Classic Egg & Cheese with (Ham, Bacon,
        or Sausage). Egg White Omelet (Veggie). Egg White Omelet with (Ham, Bacon, or Sausage). Egg & Cheese
         Wrap. Egg & Cheese Wrap with (Ham, Bacon, or Sausage). Angus Steak and Egg Wrap (Limited Time).
          Angus Steak and Egg Sandwich (Limited Time). Angus Steak and Egg Sandwich with Hash Browns & Medium
           Hot Coffee (Limited Time). Oatmeal with Medium Coffee. Turkey Sausage Wrap. Turkey Sausage Sandwich.
            Turkey Sausage Flatbread with Hash Browns & Medium Hot Coffee. Chicken Apple Sausage Breakfast Sandwich
             (Limited Time). Chicken Apple Sausage Breakfast Sandwich with Hash Browns & Medium Hot Coffee (Limited Time).</p>
    <p><b>Bakery Favorites</b> Donut. Muffin. Bagel. Munchkins. Hash Brown. Croissant. Fancy. Coffee Roll.</p>
    <p><b>Beverages</b> Coffee. Iced Coffee. Add a Turbo Shot of Espresso to Any Beverage. Add Almond Milk. Dunkaccino.
     Vanilla Chai. Cappuccino. Macchiatto. Iced Macchiatto. Box O\' Joe. Hot Chocolate. Hot Tea. Latte. Iced Latte.
      Latte Lite. Iced Latte Lite. Iced Tea or Iced Green Tea (Sweetened or Unsweetened). Coolatta or Coolatta Lite.
       Frozen Coffee. Frozen Dunkaccino. Smotthie - Tropical Mango or Strawberry Banana (Limited Time).
        Packaged Coffee (Limited Time). K-Cup Packs (Limited Time).</p>
    <p><b>Sandwiches</b> Chicken Biscuit. Texas Toast Grilled Cheese. Tune Salad. Chicken Salad. Ham & Cheese Sandwich. Turkey, Cheddar & Bacon Sandwich.</p>
    ]]></string>
    <string name="FAQ"><![CDATA[
    <h1>Frequently Asked Questions</h1>
    <p>Q: I am a resident freshman, what are my meal plan options?<br>A: All freshmen are required
     to contract for the Super Value Meal Plan or the Value 15 Meal Plan.</p>
    <p>Q: I am an upperclassman living in an on-campus residence hall/suite, what are my meal plan
     options?<br>A: All on-campus hall/suite residents are required to contract for the Super Value,
      Value 15, or Value 12 Meal Plans.</p>
     <p>Q: I live in an apartment, what are my meal plan options?<br>A: Residents of both on and off
      campus apartments are eligible for any of the meal plans. Super Value, Value 15, Value 10,
       APARTMENT Plan or the BLOCK 60 Plan.</p>
      <p>Q: What are the meal plan block-out dates?<br>A: Meal plans are not in effect during Thanksgiving,
       Semester, and Spring Breaks.</p>
      <p>Q: What if I want to make a change to meal plan?<br>A: The date for the fall semester deadline
       for residents of mandatory meal plan areas to lower their meal plan is September 22. The date
        for the spring semester deadline for residents of mandatory meal plan areas to lower their
         meal plan is February 2, 2017. Any changes made after these dates must be completed in person
          at the Residential Center. Residents of any area can increase or add a meal plan at any time.</p>
       <p>Q: What is the difference between Discretionary Dollars and Falcon Funds?<br>A: Discretionary
        Dollars are part of the Meal Plan. They may only be used to purchase food at Campus Dining
         locations (except Dunkin Donuts). Falcon Funds are money that you personally add to your Falcon
          Fund account. They may be used on campus like a debit card. Falcon Funds are accepted at the
           bookstore, student information desk and all campus dining locations.</p>
    ]]></string>




</resources>
